http://www.newmangroup.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
The Newman Group, Inc. respects your privacy. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you give us permission. We may collect, store, and use nonpublic information about you (“Your Information”) which can include name, address, telephone numbers, email address and other information, only to the extent that you have actively provided such information by completing one or more forms on our website or via e-mail.
Your Information is used to provide you with information that you have specifically requested via our website. We will not retain Your Information in a database nor will we use it to send you further communications regarding our firm or our services.
We will not sell, rent or share Your Information to anyone outside our organization.
By providing us with Your Information, or by continuing to use this website, you are consenting to our collection, storage and use of Your Information. If you wish to have Your Information removed from our database, you may contact us in writing or by email.
“Other Information,” given by you as a result of your visit to this website, is information that cannot be used to identify you; it may be included in databases owned and maintained by us. We retain all rights to these databases and the information contained in them. Our website, like nearly all sites on the Internet, may use Other Information and pool Other Information with information tracking the total number of visitors to our site, the number of visitors to each page of our site, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers.
We do not use cookies and we do not partner with or have relationships with any ad server companies.
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, however, we will make the updated policy available on this page.
Privacy Policy was last modified: October 27th, 2020 by admin
The Newman Group, Inc. New York, NY
hello@newmangroup.com
Copyright ©1998-2020 The Newman Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Read our Privacy Policy.
Top
By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies
I understand
